# JAEHYEONG JO

85, Hoegi-ro, Dongdaemun-gu, Seoul, 02455, Rep. of KOREA

Email: harryjo97@kaist.ac.kr \lefthame: https://harryjo97.github.io/ \lefthame Github: /harryjo97

#### RESEARCH INTERESTS

My research interest mainly focuses on understanding physical systems through the lens of graph-structured data and its geometric symmetries. In particular, I've been focusing on the generation of the graph with diffusion models and its applications to real-world tasks, for example, drug discovery or protein design.

#### **PUBLICATIONS**

## Graph Generation with Destination-Driven Diffusion Mixture

Jaehyeong Jo\*, Dongki Kim\*, and Sung Ju Hwang

Preprint, arXiv:2302.03596

# Exploring Chemical Space with Score-based Out-of-distribution Generation

Seul Lee, Jaehyeong Jo, and Sung Ju Hwang

Preprint, arXiv:2206.07632

# Score-based Generative Modeling of Graphs via the System of Stochastic Differential Equations

Jaehyeong Jo\*, Seul Lee\*, and Sung Ju Hwang

International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML), 2022

# Edge Representation Learning with Hypergraphs

<u>Jaehyeong Jo</u>\*, Jinheon Baek\*, Seul Lee\*, Dongki Kim, Minki Kang and Sung Ju Hwang Neural Information Processing Systems (**NeurIPS**), 2021

#### RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

#### MLAI (Machine Learning & Artificial Intelligence) Lab, KAIST

Seoul, Korea

Research Assistant (Advisor: Prof. Sung Ju Hwang)

Sep. 2021 - Present

· Conducting research on graph generative model with applications to drug discovery.

Kimlab, UofT Toronto, Canada

Visiting student (Host: Prof. Philip Kim)

Feb. 2023 - Feb. 2023

· Conducting research on protein generative model with diffusion models.

#### PAI (Probability Artificial Intelligence) Lab, KAIST

Daejeon, Korea

Research Assistant (Advisor: Prof. Ganguk Hwang)

Mar. 2020 - Aug. 2021

· Conducted research on graphs (edge representation learning using hypergraph structure).

# **TALKS**

# Generation of Graph-Structured Data with Diffusion Models

Toronto, Canada

in University of Toronto (UofT)

Feb 2023

#### Score-based Generative Modeling of Graphs via the SDEs

in LoGaG: Learning on Graphs and Geometry Reading Group

Online Oct. 2022

#### Learning with Graph Structure Data

in Pohang University of Science and Technology (POSTECH)

Pohang, Korea July 2022

<sup>\*</sup> denotes equal contribution.

# Score-based Graph Generation for Material Design

in Samsung Advanced Institute of Technology (SAIT)

Suwon, Korea Jun. 2022

## **EDUCATION**

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

Ph.D. in Artificial Intelligence

Sep. 2021 - Present

Advisor: Proffesor Sung Ju Hwang

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

Daejeon, Korea

M.S. in Mathematical Sciences Mar. 2020 - Aug. 2021

Advisor: Professor Ganguk Hwang

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

Daejeon, Korea

B.S. in Mathematical Sciences

Mar. 2016 - Feb. 2020

Minor in Computer Science & Engineering

GPA: 3.75/4.3

#### ACADEMIC SERVICES

#### Conference Reviewers

- · Learning on Graphs Conference (LoG), 2022
- · Conference on Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS), 2022
- · International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML), 2022